The war on drugs has never been about drugs.
The House I Live In is a documentary film directed by Eugene Jarecki.
In the past 40 years, the War on Drugs has accounted for 45 million arrests, made America the
world's largest jailer, and destroyed impoverished communities at home and abroad.
Yet drugs are cheaper, purer, and more available today than ever.
Where did we go wrong?
Himself - Narrator / Interviewer, played by Eugene Jarecki.
Self (archive footage) (uncredited), played by Joe Biden.
Self (archive footage) (uncredited), played by George H. W. Bush.
Self (archive footage) (uncredited), played by Rudolph Giuliani.
Self (archive footage) (uncredited), played by John McCain.
Self (archive footage) (uncredited), played by Nelson Rockefeller.
The House I Live In, directed by Eugene Jarecki, is a 2012
documentary film about the war on drugs in the United States.
The film explores themes of prison, government regulation, drug war.